const questions = [{'question': 'What are the adjustable parameters in the Neurons called?', 'options': ['Weights', 'Activators', 'Functions', 'Delays'], 'answer': 'Weights'}, {'question': 'Systems that only react without creating memories or using any past experiences are called:', 'options': ['Limited Memory Systems', 'Reactive Machines', 'Learning Agents', 'Cognitive Systems'], 'answer': 'Reactive Machines'}, {'question': 'Deep learning uses multiple layers of Neural Networks to process unstructured data, unlike Machine Learning which relies on:', 'options': ['Structured Data', 'Rules', 'Labels', 'Algorithms'], 'answer': 'Structured Data'}, {'question': 'Just like the PC, Internet and Cloud Computing, AI is also a:', 'options': ['Disruptive Technology', 'Linear Model', 'Simple Process', 'Rule-Based System'], 'answer': 'Disruptive Technology'}, {'question': 'What tasks can wearable fitness technology perform in addition to step counting?', 'options': ['Monitoring heart rate', 'Sending messages', 'Analyzing DNA', 'Generating passwords'], 'answer': 'Monitoring heart rate'}, {'question': 'Sample question 6?', 'options': ['Option A6', 'Option B6', 'Option C6', 'Option D6'], 'answer': 'Option A6'}, {'question': 'Sample question 7?', 'options': ['Option A7', 'Option B7', 'Option C7', 'Option D7'], 'answer': 'Option A7'}, {'question': 'Sample question 8?', 'options': ['Option A8', 'Option B8', 'Option C8', 'Option D8'], 'answer': 'Option A8'}, {'question': 'Sample question 9?', 'options': ['Option A9', 'Option B9', 'Option C9', 'Option D9'], 'answer': 'Option A9'}, {'question': 'Sample question 10?', 'options': ['Option A10', 'Option B10', 'Option C10', 'Option D10'], 'answer': 'Option A10'}, {'question': 'Sample question 11?', 'options': ['Option A11', 'Option B11', 'Option C11', 'Option D11'], 'answer': 'Option A11'}, {'question': 'Sample question 12?', 'options': ['Option A12', 'Option B12', 'Option C12', 'Option D12'], 'answer': 'Option A12'}, {'question': 'Sample question 13?', 'options': ['Option A13', 'Option B13', 'Option C13', 'Option D13'], 'answer': 'Option A13'}, {'question': 'Sample question 14?', 'options': ['Option A14', 'Option B14', 'Option C14', 'Option D14'], 'answer': 'Option A14'}, {'question': 'Sample question 15?', 'options': ['Option A15', 'Option B15', 'Option C15', 'Option D15'], 'answer': 'Option A15'}, {'question': 'Sample question 16?', 'options': ['Option A16', 'Option B16', 'Option C16', 'Option D16'], 'answer': 'Option A16'}, {'question': 'Sample question 17?', 'options': ['Option A17', 'Option B17', 'Option C17', 'Option D17'], 'answer': 'Option A17'}, {'question': 'Sample question 18?', 'options': ['Option A18', 'Option B18', 'Option C18', 'Option D18'], 'answer': 'Option A18'}, {'question': 'Sample question 19?', 'options': ['Option A19', 'Option B19', 'Option C19', 'Option D19'], 'answer': 'Option A19'}, {'question': 'Sample question 20?', 'options': ['Option A20', 'Option B20', 'Option C20', 'Option D20'], 'answer': 'Option A20'}, {'question': 'Sample question 21?', 'options': ['Option A21', 'Option B21', 'Option C21', 'Option D21'], 'answer': 'Option A21'}, {'question': 'Sample question 22?', 'options': ['Option A22', 'Option B22', 'Option C22', 'Option D22'], 'answer': 'Option A22'}, {'question': 'Sample question 23?', 'options': ['Option A23', 'Option B23', 'Option C23', 'Option D23'], 'answer': 'Option A23'}, {'question': 'Sample question 24?', 'options': ['Option A24', 'Option B24', 'Option C24', 'Option D24'], 'answer': 'Option A24'}, {'question': 'Sample question 25?', 'options': ['Option A25', 'Option B25', 'Option C25', 'Option D25'], 'answer': 'Option A25'}, {'question': 'Sample question 26?', 'options': ['Option A26', 'Option B26', 'Option C26', 'Option D26'], 'answer': 'Option A26'}, {'question': 'Sample question 27?', 'options': ['Option A27', 'Option B27', 'Option C27', 'Option D27'], 'answer': 'Option A27'}, {'question': 'Sample question 28?', 'options': ['Option A28', 'Option B28', 'Option C28', 'Option D28'], 'answer': 'Option A28'}, {'question': 'Sample question 29?', 'options': ['Option A29', 'Option B29', 'Option C29', 'Option D29'], 'answer': 'Option A29'}, {'question': 'Sample question 30?', 'options': ['Option A30', 'Option B30', 'Option C30', 'Option D30'], 'answer': 'Option A30'}, {'question': 'Sample question 31?', 'options': ['Option A31', 'Option B31', 'Option C31', 'Option D31'], 'answer': 'Option A31'}, {'question': 'Sample question 32?', 'options': ['Option A32', 'Option B32', 'Option C32', 'Option D32'], 'answer': 'Option A32'}, {'question': 'Sample question 33?', 'options': ['Option A33', 'Option B33', 'Option C33', 'Option D33'], 'answer': 'Option A33'}, {'question': 'Sample question 34?', 'options': ['Option A34', 'Option B34', 'Option C34', 'Option D34'], 'answer': 'Option A34'}, {'question': 'Sample question 35?', 'options': ['Option A35', 'Option B35', 'Option C35', 'Option D35'], 'answer': 'Option A35'}, {'question': 'Sample question 36?', 'options': ['Option A36', 'Option B36', 'Option C36', 'Option D36'], 'answer': 'Option A36'}, {'question': 'Sample question 37?', 'options': ['Option A37', 'Option B37', 'Option C37', 'Option D37'], 'answer': 'Option A37'}, {'question': 'Sample question 38?', 'options': ['Option A38', 'Option B38', 'Option C38', 'Option D38'], 'answer': 'Option A38'}, {'question': 'Sample question 39?', 'options': ['Option A39', 'Option B39', 'Option C39', 'Option D39'], 'answer': 'Option A39'}, {'question': 'Sample question 40?', 'options': ['Option A40', 'Option B40', 'Option C40', 'Option D40'], 'answer': 'Option A40'}, {'question': 'Sample question 41?', 'options': ['Option A41', 'Option B41', 'Option C41', 'Option D41'], 'answer': 'Option A41'}, {'question': 'Sample question 42?', 'options': ['Option A42', 'Option B42', 'Option C42', 'Option D42'], 'answer': 'Option A42'}, {'question': 'Sample question 43?', 'options': ['Option A43', 'Option B43', 'Option C43', 'Option D43'], 'answer': 'Option A43'}, {'question': 'Sample question 44?', 'options': ['Option A44', 'Option B44', 'Option C44', 'Option D44'], 'answer': 'Option A44'}, {'question': 'Sample question 45?', 'options': ['Option A45', 'Option B45', 'Option C45', 'Option D45'], 'answer': 'Option A45'}, {'question': 'Sample question 46?', 'options': ['Option A46', 'Option B46', 'Option C46', 'Option D46'], 'answer': 'Option A46'}, {'question': 'Sample question 47?', 'options': ['Option A47', 'Option B47', 'Option C47', 'Option D47'], 'answer': 'Option A47'}, {'question': 'Sample question 48?', 'options': ['Option A48', 'Option B48', 'Option C48', 'Option D48'], 'answer': 'Option A48'}, {'question': 'Sample question 49?', 'options': ['Option A49', 'Option B49', 'Option C49', 'Option D49'], 'answer': 'Option A49'}, {'question': 'Sample question 50?', 'options': ['Option A50', 'Option B50', 'Option C50', 'Option D50'], 'answer': 'Option A50'}, {'question': 'Sample question 51?', 'options': ['Option A51', 'Option B51', 'Option C51', 'Option D51'], 'answer': 'Option A51'}, {'question': 'Sample question 52?', 'options': ['Option A52', 'Option B52', 'Option C52', 'Option D52'], 'answer': 'Option A52'}, {'question': 'Sample question 53?', 'options': ['Option A53', 'Option B53', 'Option C53', 'Option D53'], 'answer': 'Option A53'}, {'question': 'Sample question 54?', 'options': ['Option A54', 'Option B54', 'Option C54', 'Option D54'], 'answer': 'Option A54'}, {'question': 'Sample question 55?', 'options': ['Option A55', 'Option B55', 'Option C55', 'Option D55'], 'answer': 'Option A55'}, {'question': 'Sample question 56?', 'options': ['Option A56', 'Option B56', 'Option C56', 'Option D56'], 'answer': 'Option A56'}, {'question': 'Sample question 57?', 'options': ['Option A57', 'Option B57', 'Option C57', 'Option D57'], 'answer': 'Option A57'}, {'question': 'Sample question 58?', 'options': ['Option A58', 'Option B58', 'Option C58', 'Option D58'], 'answer': 'Option A58'}, {'question': 'Sample question 59?', 'options': ['Option A59', 'Option B59', 'Option C59', 'Option D59'], 'answer': 'Option A59'}, {'question': 'Sample question 60?', 'options': ['Option A60', 'Option B60', 'Option C60', 'Option D60'], 'answer': 'Option A60'}, {'question': 'Sample question 61?', 'options': ['Option A61', 'Option B61', 'Option C61', 'Option D61'], 'answer': 'Option A61'}, {'question': 'Sample question 62?', 'options': ['Option A62', 'Option B62', 'Option C62', 'Option D62'], 'answer': 'Option A62'}, {'question': 'Sample question 63?', 'options': ['Option A63', 'Option B63', 'Option C63', 'Option D63'], 'answer': 'Option A63'}, {'question': 'Sample question 64?', 'options': ['Option A64', 'Option B64', 'Option C64', 'Option D64'], 'answer': 'Option A64'}, {'question': 'Sample question 65?', 'options': ['Option A65', 'Option B65', 'Option C65', 'Option D65'], 'answer': 'Option A65'}, {'question': 'Sample question 66?', 'options': ['Option A66', 'Option B66', 'Option C66', 'Option D66'], 'answer': 'Option A66'}, {'question': 'Sample question 67?', 'options': ['Option A67', 'Option B67', 'Option C67', 'Option D67'], 'answer': 'Option A67'}, {'question': 'Sample question 68?', 'options': ['Option A68', 'Option B68', 'Option C68', 'Option D68'], 'answer': 'Option A68'}, {'question': 'Sample question 69?', 'options': ['Option A69', 'Option B69', 'Option C69', 'Option D69'], 'answer': 'Option A69'}, {'question': 'Sample question 70?', 'options': ['Option A70', 'Option B70', 'Option C70', 'Option D70'], 'answer': 'Option A70'}, {'question': 'Sample question 71?', 'options': ['Option A71', 'Option B71', 'Option C71', 'Option D71'], 'answer': 'Option A71'}, {'question': 'Sample question 72?', 'options': ['Option A72', 'Option B72', 'Option C72', 'Option D72'], 'answer': 'Option A72'}, {'question': 'Sample question 73?', 'options': ['Option A73', 'Option B73', 'Option C73', 'Option D73'], 'answer': 'Option A73'}, {'question': 'Sample question 74?', 'options': ['Option A74', 'Option B74', 'Option C74', 'Option D74'], 'answer': 'Option A74'}, {'question': 'Sample question 75?', 'options': ['Option A75', 'Option B75', 'Option C75', 'Option D75'], 'answer': 'Option A75'}, {'question': 'Sample question 76?', 'options': ['Option A76', 'Option B76', 'Option C76', 'Option D76'], 'answer': 'Option A76'}, {'question': 'Sample question 77?', 'options': ['Option A77', 'Option B77', 'Option C77', 'Option D77'], 'answer': 'Option A77'}, {'question': 'Sample question 78?', 'options': ['Option A78', 'Option B78', 'Option C78', 'Option D78'], 'answer': 'Option A78'}, {'question': 'Sample question 79?', 'options': ['Option A79', 'Option B79', 'Option C79', 'Option D79'], 'answer': 'Option A79'}, {'question': 'Sample question 80?', 'options': ['Option A80', 'Option B80', 'Option C80', 'Option D80'], 'answer': 'Option A80'}, {'question': 'Sample question 81?', 'options': ['Option A81', 'Option B81', 'Option C81', 'Option D81'], 'answer': 'Option A81'}, {'question': 'Sample question 82?', 'options': ['Option A82', 'Option B82', 'Option C82', 'Option D82'], 'answer': 'Option A82'}, {'question': 'Sample question 83?', 'options': ['Option A83', 'Option B83', 'Option C83', 'Option D83'], 'answer': 'Option A83'}, {'question': 'Sample question 84?', 'options': ['Option A84', 'Option B84', 'Option C84', 'Option D84'], 'answer': 'Option A84'}, {'question': 'Sample question 85?', 'options': ['Option A85', 'Option B85', 'Option C85', 'Option D85'], 'answer': 'Option A85'}, {'question': 'Sample question 86?', 'options': ['Option A86', 'Option B86', 'Option C86', 'Option D86'], 'answer': 'Option A86'}, {'question': 'Sample question 87?', 'options': ['Option A87', 'Option B87', 'Option C87', 'Option D87'], 'answer': 'Option A87'}, {'question': 'Sample question 88?', 'options': ['Option A88', 'Option B88', 'Option C88', 'Option D88'], 'answer': 'Option A88'}, {'question': 'Sample question 89?', 'options': ['Option A89', 'Option B89', 'Option C89', 'Option D89'], 'answer': 'Option A89'}, {'question': 'Sample question 90?', 'options': ['Option A90', 'Option B90', 'Option C90', 'Option D90'], 'answer': 'Option A90'}, {'question': 'Sample question 91?', 'options': ['Option A91', 'Option B91', 'Option C91', 'Option D91'], 'answer': 'Option A91'}, {'question': 'Sample question 92?', 'options': ['Option A92', 'Option B92', 'Option C92', 'Option D92'], 'answer': 'Option A92'}, {'question': 'Sample question 93?', 'options': ['Option A93', 'Option B93', 'Option C93', 'Option D93'], 'answer': 'Option A93'}, {'question': 'Sample question 94?', 'options': ['Option A94', 'Option B94', 'Option C94', 'Option D94'], 'answer': 'Option A94'}, {'question': 'Sample question 95?', 'options': ['Option A95', 'Option B95', 'Option C95', 'Option D95'], 'answer': 'Option A95'}, {'question': 'Sample question 96?', 'options': ['Option A96', 'Option B96', 'Option C96', 'Option D96'], 'answer': 'Option A96'}, {'question': 'Sample question 97?', 'options': ['Option A97', 'Option B97', 'Option C97', 'Option D97'], 'answer': 'Option A97'}, {'question': 'Sample question 98?', 'options': ['Option A98', 'Option B98', 'Option C98', 'Option D98'], 'answer': 'Option A98'}, {'question': 'Sample question 99?', 'options': ['Option A99', 'Option B99', 'Option C99', 'Option D99'], 'answer': 'Option A99'}, {'question': 'Sample question 100?', 'options': ['Option A100', 'Option B100', 'Option C100', 'Option D100'], 'answer': 'Option A100'}, {'question': 'Sample question 101?', 'options': ['Option A101', 'Option B101', 'Option C101', 'Option D101'], 'answer': 'Option A101'}, {'question': 'Sample question 102?', 'options': ['Option A102', 'Option B102', 'Option C102', 'Option D102'], 'answer': 'Option A102'}, {'question': 'Sample question 103?', 'options': ['Option A103', 'Option B103', 'Option C103', 'Option D103'], 'answer': 'Option A103'}, {'question': 'Sample question 104?', 'options': ['Option A104', 'Option B104', 'Option C104', 'Option D104'], 'answer': 'Option A104'}, {'question': 'Sample question 105?', 'options': ['Option A105', 'Option B105', 'Option C105', 'Option D105'], 'answer': 'Option A105'}, {'question': 'Sample question 106?', 'options': ['Option A106', 'Option B106', 'Option C106', 'Option D106'], 'answer': 'Option A106'}, {'question': 'Sample question 107?', 'options': ['Option A107', 'Option B107', 'Option C107', 'Option D107'], 'answer': 'Option A107'}, {'question': 'Sample question 108?', 'options': ['Option A108', 'Option B108', 'Option C108', 'Option D108'], 'answer': 'Option A108'}, {'question': 'Sample question 109?', 'options': ['Option A109', 'Option B109', 'Option C109', 'Option D109'], 'answer': 'Option A109'}, {'question': 'Sample question 110?', 'options': ['Option A110', 'Option B110', 'Option C110', 'Option D110'], 'answer': 'Option A110'}, {'question': 'Sample question 111?', 'options': ['Option A111', 'Option B111', 'Option C111', 'Option D111'], 'answer': 'Option A111'}, {'question': 'Sample question 112?', 'options': ['Option A112', 'Option B112', 'Option C112', 'Option D112'], 'answer': 'Option A112'}, {'question': 'Sample question 113?', 'options': ['Option A113', 'Option B113', 'Option C113', 'Option D113'], 'answer': 'Option A113'}, {'question': 'Sample question 114?', 'options': ['Option A114', 'Option B114', 'Option C114', 'Option D114'], 'answer': 'Option A114'}, {'question': 'Sample question 115?', 'options': ['Option A115', 'Option B115', 'Option C115', 'Option D115'], 'answer': 'Option A115'}, {'question': 'Sample question 116?', 'options': ['Option A116', 'Option B116', 'Option C116', 'Option D116'], 'answer': 'Option A116'}, {'question': 'Sample question 117?', 'options': ['Option A117', 'Option B117', 'Option C117', 'Option D117'], 'answer': 'Option A117'}, {'question': 'Sample question 118?', 'options': ['Option A118', 'Option B118', 'Option C118', 'Option D118'], 'answer': 'Option A118'}, {'question': 'Sample question 119?', 'options': ['Option A119', 'Option B119', 'Option C119', 'Option D119'], 'answer': 'Option A119'}, {'question': 'Sample question 120?', 'options': ['Option A120', 'Option B120', 'Option C120', 'Option D120'], 'answer': 'Option A120'}, {'question': 'Sample question 121?', 'options': ['Option A121', 'Option B121', 'Option C121', 'Option D121'], 'answer': 'Option A121'}, {'question': 'Sample question 122?', 'options': ['Option A122', 'Option B122', 'Option C122', 'Option D122'], 'answer': 'Option A122'}, {'question': 'Sample question 123?', 'options': ['Option A123', 'Option B123', 'Option C123', 'Option D123'], 'answer': 'Option A123'}, {'question': 'Sample question 124?', 'options': ['Option A124', 'Option B124', 'Option C124', 'Option D124'], 'answer': 'Option A124'}, {'question': 'Sample question 125?', 'options': ['Option A125', 'Option B125', 'Option C125', 'Option D125'], 'answer': 'Option A125'}, {'question': 'Sample question 126?', 'options': ['Option A126', 'Option B126', 'Option C126', 'Option D126'], 'answer': 'Option A126'}, {'question': 'Sample question 127?', 'options': ['Option A127', 'Option B127', 'Option C127', 'Option D127'], 'answer': 'Option A127'}, {'question': 'Sample question 128?', 'options': ['Option A128', 'Option B128', 'Option C128', 'Option D128'], 'answer': 'Option A128'}, {'question': 'Sample question 129?', 'options': ['Option A129', 'Option B129', 'Option C129', 'Option D129'], 'answer': 'Option A129'}, {'question': 'Sample question 130?', 'options': ['Option A130', 'Option B130', 'Option C130', 'Option D130'], 'answer': 'Option A130'}, {'question': 'Sample question 131?', 'options': ['Option A131', 'Option B131', 'Option C131', 'Option D131'], 'answer': 'Option A131'}, {'question': 'Sample question 132?', 'options': ['Option A132', 'Option B132', 'Option C132', 'Option D132'], 'answer': 'Option A132'}, {'question': 'Sample question 133?', 'options': ['Option A133', 'Option B133', 'Option C133', 'Option D133'], 'answer': 'Option A133'}, {'question': 'Sample question 134?', 'options': ['Option A134', 'Option B134', 'Option C134', 'Option D134'], 'answer': 'Option A134'}, {'question': 'Sample question 135?', 'options': ['Option A135', 'Option B135', 'Option C135', 'Option D135'], 'answer': 'Option A135'}, {'question': 'Sample question 136?', 'options': ['Option A136', 'Option B136', 'Option C136', 'Option D136'], 'answer': 'Option A136'}, {'question': 'Sample question 137?', 'options': ['Option A137', 'Option B137', 'Option C137', 'Option D137'], 'answer': 'Option A137'}, {'question': 'Sample question 138?', 'options': ['Option A138', 'Option B138', 'Option C138', 'Option D138'], 'answer': 'Option A138'}, {'question': 'Sample question 139?', 'options': ['Option A139', 'Option B139', 'Option C139', 'Option D139'], 'answer': 'Option A139'}, {'question': 'Sample question 140?', 'options': ['Option A140', 'Option B140', 'Option C140', 'Option D140'], 'answer': 'Option A140'}, {'question': 'Sample question 141?', 'options': ['Option A141', 'Option B141', 'Option C141', 'Option D141'], 'answer': 'Option A141'}, {'question': 'Sample question 142?', 'options': ['Option A142', 'Option B142', 'Option C142', 'Option D142'], 'answer': 'Option A142'}, {'question': 'Sample question 143?', 'options': ['Option A143', 'Option B143', 'Option C143', 'Option D143'], 'answer': 'Option A143'}, {'question': 'Sample question 144?', 'options': ['Option A144', 'Option B144', 'Option C144', 'Option D144'], 'answer': 'Option A144'}, {'question': 'Sample question 145?', 'options': ['Option A145', 'Option B145', 'Option C145', 'Option D145'], 'answer': 'Option A145'}, {'question': 'Sample question 146?', 'options': ['Option A146', 'Option B146', 'Option C146', 'Option D146'], 'answer': 'Option A146'}, {'question': 'Sample question 147?', 'options': ['Option A147', 'Option B147', 'Option C147', 'Option D147'], 'answer': 'Option A147'}, {'question': 'Sample question 148?', 'options': ['Option A148', 'Option B148', 'Option C148', 'Option D148'], 'answer': 'Option A148'}, {'question': 'Sample question 149?', 'options': ['Option A149', 'Option B149', 'Option C149', 'Option D149'], 'answer': 'Option A149'}, {'question': 'Sample question 150?', 'options': ['Option A150', 'Option B150', 'Option C150', 'Option D150'], 'answer': 'Option A150'}, {'question': 'Sample question 151?', 'options': ['Option A151', 'Option B151', 'Option C151', 'Option D151'], 'answer': 'Option A151'}, {'question': 'Sample question 152?', 'options': ['Option A152', 'Option B152', 'Option C152', 'Option D152'], 'answer': 'Option A152'}, {'question': 'Sample question 153?', 'options': ['Option A153', 'Option B153', 'Option C153', 'Option D153'], 'answer': 'Option A153'}, {'question': 'Sample question 154?', 'options': ['Option A154', 'Option B154', 'Option C154', 'Option D154'], 'answer': 'Option A154'}, {'question': 'Sample question 155?', 'options': ['Option A155', 'Option B155', 'Option C155', 'Option D155'], 'answer': 'Option A155'}, {'question': 'Sample question 156?', 'options': ['Option A156', 'Option B156', 'Option C156', 'Option D156'], 'answer': 'Option A156'}, {'question': 'Sample question 157?', 'options': ['Option A157', 'Option B157', 'Option C157', 'Option D157'], 'answer': 'Option A157'}, {'question': 'Sample question 158?', 'options': ['Option A158', 'Option B158', 'Option C158', 'Option D158'], 'answer': 'Option A158'}, {'question': 'Sample question 159?', 'options': ['Option A159', 'Option B159', 'Option C159', 'Option D159'], 'answer': 'Option A159'}, {'question': 'Sample question 160?', 'options': ['Option A160', 'Option B160', 'Option C160', 'Option D160'], 'answer': 'Option A160'}, {'question': 'Sample question 161?', 'options': ['Option A161', 'Option B161', 'Option C161', 'Option D161'], 'answer': 'Option A161'}, {'question': 'Sample question 162?', 'options': ['Option A162', 'Option B162', 'Option C162', 'Option D162'], 'answer': 'Option A162'}, {'question': 'Sample question 163?', 'options': ['Option A163', 'Option B163', 'Option C163', 'Option D163'], 'answer': 'Option A163'}, {'question': 'Sample question 164?', 'options': ['Option A164', 'Option B164', 'Option C164', 'Option D164'], 'answer': 'Option A164'}, {'question': 'Sample question 165?', 'options': ['Option A165', 'Option B165', 'Option C165', 'Option D165'], 'answer': 'Option A165'}, {'question': 'Sample question 166?', 'options': ['Option A166', 'Option B166', 'Option C166', 'Option D166'], 'answer': 'Option A166'}, {'question': 'Sample question 167?', 'options': ['Option A167', 'Option B167', 'Option C167', 'Option D167'], 'answer': 'Option A167'}, {'question': 'Sample question 168?', 'options': ['Option A168', 'Option B168', 'Option C168', 'Option D168'], 'answer': 'Option A168'}, {'question': 'Sample question 169?', 'options': ['Option A169', 'Option B169', 'Option C169', 'Option D169'], 'answer': 'Option A169'}, {'question': 'Sample question 170?', 'options': ['Option A170', 'Option B170', 'Option C170', 'Option D170'], 'answer': 'Option A170'}, {'question': 'Sample question 171?', 'options': ['Option A171', 'Option B171', 'Option C171', 'Option D171'], 'answer': 'Option A171'}, {'question': 'Sample question 172?', 'options': ['Option A172', 'Option B172', 'Option C172', 'Option D172'], 'answer': 'Option A172'}, {'question': 'Sample question 173?', 'options': ['Option A173', 'Option B173', 'Option C173', 'Option D173'], 'answer': 'Option A173'}, {'question': 'Sample question 174?', 'options': ['Option A174', 'Option B174', 'Option C174', 'Option D174'], 'answer': 'Option A174'}, {'question': 'Sample question 175?', 'options': ['Option A175', 'Option B175', 'Option C175', 'Option D175'], 'answer': 'Option A175'}, {'question': 'Sample question 176?', 'options': ['Option A176', 'Option B176', 'Option C176', 'Option D176'], 'answer': 'Option A176'}, {'question': 'Sample question 177?', 'options': ['Option A177', 'Option B177', 'Option C177', 'Option D177'], 'answer': 'Option A177'}, {'question': 'Sample question 178?', 'options': ['Option A178', 'Option B178', 'Option C178', 'Option D178'], 'answer': 'Option A178'}, {'question': 'Sample question 179?', 'options': ['Option A179', 'Option B179', 'Option C179', 'Option D179'], 'answer': 'Option A179'}, {'question': 'Sample question 180?', 'options': ['Option A180', 'Option B180', 'Option C180', 'Option D180'], 'answer': 'Option A180'}, {'question': 'Sample question 181?', 'options': ['Option A181', 'Option B181', 'Option C181', 'Option D181'], 'answer': 'Option A181'}, {'question': 'Sample question 182?', 'options': ['Option A182', 'Option B182', 'Option C182', 'Option D182'], 'answer': 'Option A182'}, {'question': 'Sample question 183?', 'options': ['Option A183', 'Option B183', 'Option C183', 'Option D183'], 'answer': 'Option A183'}, {'question': 'Sample question 184?', 'options': ['Option A184', 'Option B184', 'Option C184', 'Option D184'], 'answer': 'Option A184'}, {'question': 'Sample question 185?', 'options': ['Option A185', 'Option B185', 'Option C185', 'Option D185'], 'answer': 'Option A185'}, {'question': 'Sample question 186?', 'options': ['Option A186', 'Option B186', 'Option C186', 'Option D186'], 'answer': 'Option A186'}, {'question': 'Sample question 187?', 'options': ['Option A187', 'Option B187', 'Option C187', 'Option D187'], 'answer': 'Option A187'}, {'question': 'Sample question 188?', 'options': ['Option A188', 'Option B188', 'Option C188', 'Option D188'], 'answer': 'Option A188'}, {'question': 'Sample question 189?', 'options': ['Option A189', 'Option B189', 'Option C189', 'Option D189'], 'answer': 'Option A189'}, {'question': 'Sample question 190?', 'options': ['Option A190', 'Option B190', 'Option C190', 'Option D190'], 'answer': 'Option A190'}, {'question': 'Sample question 191?', 'options': ['Option A191', 'Option B191', 'Option C191', 'Option D191'], 'answer': 'Option A191'}, {'question': 'Sample question 192?', 'options': ['Option A192', 'Option B192', 'Option C192', 'Option D192'], 'answer': 'Option A192'}, {'question': 'Sample question 193?', 'options': ['Option A193', 'Option B193', 'Option C193', 'Option D193'], 'answer': 'Option A193'}, {'question': 'Sample question 194?', 'options': ['Option A194', 'Option B194', 'Option C194', 'Option D194'], 'answer': 'Option A194'}, {'question': 'Sample question 195?', 'options': ['Option A195', 'Option B195', 'Option C195', 'Option D195'], 'answer': 'Option A195'}, {'question': 'Sample question 196?', 'options': ['Option A196', 'Option B196', 'Option C196', 'Option D196'], 'answer': 'Option A196'}, {'question': 'Sample question 197?', 'options': ['Option A197', 'Option B197', 'Option C197', 'Option D197'], 'answer': 'Option A197'}, {'question': 'Sample question 198?', 'options': ['Option A198', 'Option B198', 'Option C198', 'Option D198'], 'answer': 'Option A198'}, {'question': 'Sample question 199?', 'options': ['Option A199', 'Option B199', 'Option C199', 'Option D199'], 'answer': 'Option A199'}, {'question': 'Sample question 200?', 'options': ['Option A200', 'Option B200', 'Option C200', 'Option D200'], 'answer': 'Option A200'}, {'question': 'Sample question 201?', 'options': ['Option A201', 'Option B201', 'Option C201', 'Option D201'], 'answer': 'Option A201'}, {'question': 'Sample question 202?', 'options': ['Option A202', 'Option B202', 'Option C202', 'Option D202'], 'answer': 'Option A202'}, {'question': 'Sample question 203?', 'options': ['Option A203', 'Option B203', 'Option C203', 'Option D203'], 'answer': 'Option A203'}, {'question': 'Sample question 204?', 'options': ['Option A204', 'Option B204', 'Option C204', 'Option D204'], 'answer': 'Option A204'}, {'question': 'Sample question 205?', 'options': ['Option A205', 'Option B205', 'Option C205', 'Option D205'], 'answer': 'Option A205'}, {'question': 'Sample question 206?', 'options': ['Option A206', 'Option B206', 'Option C206', 'Option D206'], 'answer': 'Option A206'}, {'question': 'Sample question 207?', 'options': ['Option A207', 'Option B207', 'Option C207', 'Option D207'], 'answer': 'Option A207'}, {'question': 'Sample question 208?', 'options': ['Option A208', 'Option B208', 'Option C208', 'Option D208'], 'answer': 'Option A208'}, {'question': 'Sample question 209?', 'options': ['Option A209', 'Option B209', 'Option C209', 'Option D209'], 'answer': 'Option A209'}, {'question': 'Sample question 210?', 'options': ['Option A210', 'Option B210', 'Option C210', 'Option D210'], 'answer': 'Option A210'}, {'question': 'Sample question 211?', 'options': ['Option A211', 'Option B211', 'Option C211', 'Option D211'], 'answer': 'Option A211'}, {'question': 'Sample question 212?', 'options': ['Option A212', 'Option B212', 'Option C212', 'Option D212'], 'answer': 'Option A212'}, {'question': 'Sample question 213?', 'options': ['Option A213', 'Option B213', 'Option C213', 'Option D213'], 'answer': 'Option A213'}, {'question': 'Sample question 214?', 'options': ['Option A214', 'Option B214', 'Option C214', 'Option D214'], 'answer': 'Option A214'}, {'question': 'Sample question 215?', 'options': ['Option A215', 'Option B215', 'Option C215', 'Option D215'], 'answer': 'Option A215'}, {'question': 'Sample question 216?', 'options': ['Option A216', 'Option B216', 'Option C216', 'Option D216'], 'answer': 'Option A216'}, {'question': 'Sample question 217?', 'options': ['Option A217', 'Option B217', 'Option C217', 'Option D217'], 'answer': 'Option A217'}, {'question': 'Sample question 218?', 'options': ['Option A218', 'Option B218', 'Option C218', 'Option D218'], 'answer': 'Option A218'}, {'question': 'Sample question 219?', 'options': ['Option A219', 'Option B219', 'Option C219', 'Option D219'], 'answer': 'Option A219'}, {'question': 'Sample question 220?', 'options': ['Option A220', 'Option B220', 'Option C220', 'Option D220'], 'answer': 'Option A220'}, {'question': 'Sample question 221?', 'options': ['Option A221', 'Option B221', 'Option C221', 'Option D221'], 'answer': 'Option A221'}, {'question': 'Sample question 222?', 'options': ['Option A222', 'Option B222', 'Option C222', 'Option D222'], 'answer': 'Option A222'}, {'question': 'Sample question 223?', 'options': ['Option A223', 'Option B223', 'Option C223', 'Option D223'], 'answer': 'Option A223'}, {'question': 'Sample question 224?', 'options': ['Option A224', 'Option B224', 'Option C224', 'Option D224'], 'answer': 'Option A224'}, {'question': 'Sample question 225?', 'options': ['Option A225', 'Option B225', 'Option C225', 'Option D225'], 'answer': 'Option A225'}, {'question': 'Sample question 226?', 'options': ['Option A226', 'Option B226', 'Option C226', 'Option D226'], 'answer': 'Option A226'}, {'question': 'Sample question 227?', 'options': ['Option A227', 'Option B227', 'Option C227', 'Option D227'], 'answer': 'Option A227'}, {'question': 'Sample question 228?', 'options': ['Option A228', 'Option B228', 'Option C228', 'Option D228'], 'answer': 'Option A228'}, {'question': 'Sample question 229?', 'options': ['Option A229', 'Option B229', 'Option C229', 'Option D229'], 'answer': 'Option A229'}, {'question': 'Sample question 230?', 'options': ['Option A230', 'Option B230', 'Option C230', 'Option D230'], 'answer': 'Option A230'}, {'question': 'Sample question 231?', 'options': ['Option A231', 'Option B231', 'Option C231', 'Option D231'], 'answer': 'Option A231'}, {'question': 'Sample question 232?', 'options': ['Option A232', 'Option B232', 'Option C232', 'Option D232'], 'answer': 'Option A232'}, {'question': 'Sample question 233?', 'options': ['Option A233', 'Option B233', 'Option C233', 'Option D233'], 'answer': 'Option A233'}, {'question': 'Sample question 234?', 'options': ['Option A234', 'Option B234', 'Option C234', 'Option D234'], 'answer': 'Option A234'}, {'question': 'Sample question 235?', 'options': ['Option A235', 'Option B235', 'Option C235', 'Option D235'], 'answer': 'Option A235'}, {'question': 'Sample question 236?', 'options': ['Option A236', 'Option B236', 'Option C236', 'Option D236'], 'answer': 'Option A236'}, {'question': 'Sample question 237?', 'options': ['Option A237', 'Option B237', 'Option C237', 'Option D237'], 'answer': 'Option A237'}, {'question': 'Sample question 238?', 'options': ['Option A238', 'Option B238', 'Option C238', 'Option D238'], 'answer': 'Option A238'}, {'question': 'Sample question 239?', 'options': ['Option A239', 'Option B239', 'Option C239', 'Option D239'], 'answer': 'Option A239'}, {'question': 'Sample question 240?', 'options': ['Option A240', 'Option B240', 'Option C240', 'Option D240'], 'answer': 'Option A240'}, {'question': 'Sample question 241?', 'options': ['Option A241', 'Option B241', 'Option C241', 'Option D241'], 'answer': 'Option A241'}, {'question': 'Sample question 242?', 'options': ['Option A242', 'Option B242', 'Option C242', 'Option D242'], 'answer': 'Option A242'}, {'question': 'Sample question 243?', 'options': ['Option A243', 'Option B243', 'Option C243', 'Option D243'], 'answer': 'Option A243'}, {'question': 'Sample question 244?', 'options': ['Option A244', 'Option B244', 'Option C244', 'Option D244'], 'answer': 'Option A244'}, {'question': 'Sample question 245?', 'options': ['Option A245', 'Option B245', 'Option C245', 'Option D245'], 'answer': 'Option A245'}, {'question': 'Sample question 246?', 'options': ['Option A246', 'Option B246', 'Option C246', 'Option D246'], 'answer': 'Option A246'}, {'question': 'Sample question 247?', 'options': ['Option A247', 'Option B247', 'Option C247', 'Option D247'], 'answer': 'Option A247'}, {'question': 'Sample question 248?', 'options': ['Option A248', 'Option B248', 'Option C248', 'Option D248'], 'answer': 'Option A248'}, {'question': 'Sample question 249?', 'options': ['Option A249', 'Option B249', 'Option C249', 'Option D249'], 'answer': 'Option A249'}, {'question': 'Sample question 250?', 'options': ['Option A250', 'Option B250', 'Option C250', 'Option D250'], 'answer': 'Option A250'}, {'question': 'Sample question 251?', 'options': ['Option A251', 'Option B251', 'Option C251', 'Option D251'], 'answer': 'Option A251'}, {'question': 'Sample question 252?', 'options': ['Option A252', 'Option B252', 'Option C252', 'Option D252'], 'answer': 'Option A252'}, {'question': 'Sample question 253?', 'options': ['Option A253', 'Option B253', 'Option C253', 'Option D253'], 'answer': 'Option A253'}, {'question': 'Sample question 254?', 'options': ['Option A254', 'Option B254', 'Option C254', 'Option D254'], 'answer': 'Option A254'}, {'question': 'Sample question 255?', 'options': ['Option A255', 'Option B255', 'Option C255', 'Option D255'], 'answer': 'Option A255'}, {'question': 'Sample question 256?', 'options': ['Option A256', 'Option B256', 'Option C256', 'Option D256'], 'answer': 'Option A256'}, {'question': 'Sample question 257?', 'options': ['Option A257', 'Option B257', 'Option C257', 'Option D257'], 'answer': 'Option A257'}, {'question': 'Sample question 258?', 'options': ['Option A258', 'Option B258', 'Option C258', 'Option D258'], 'answer': 'Option A258'}, {'question': 'Sample question 259?', 'options': ['Option A259', 'Option B259', 'Option C259', 'Option D259'], 'answer': 'Option A259'}, {'question': 'Sample question 260?', 'options': ['Option A260', 'Option B260', 'Option C260', 'Option D260'], 'answer': 'Option A260'}, {'question': 'Sample question 261?', 'options': ['Option A261', 'Option B261', 'Option C261', 'Option D261'], 'answer': 'Option A261'}, {'question': 'Sample question 262?', 'options': ['Option A262', 'Option B262', 'Option C262', 'Option D262'], 'answer': 'Option A262'}, {'question': 'Sample question 263?', 'options': ['Option A263', 'Option B263', 'Option C263', 'Option D263'], 'answer': 'Option A263'}, {'question': 'Sample question 264?', 'options': ['Option A264', 'Option B264', 'Option C264', 'Option D264'], 'answer': 'Option A264'}, {'question': 'Sample question 265?', 'options': ['Option A265', 'Option B265', 'Option C265', 'Option D265'], 'answer': 'Option A265'}, {'question': 'Sample question 266?', 'options': ['Option A266', 'Option B266', 'Option C266', 'Option D266'], 'answer': 'Option A266'}, {'question': 'Sample question 267?', 'options': ['Option A267', 'Option B267', 'Option C267', 'Option D267'], 'answer': 'Option A267'}, {'question': 'Sample question 268?', 'options': ['Option A268', 'Option B268', 'Option C268', 'Option D268'], 'answer': 'Option A268'}, {'question': 'Sample question 269?', 'options': ['Option A269', 'Option B269', 'Option C269', 'Option D269'], 'answer': 'Option A269'}, {'question': 'Sample question 270?', 'options': ['Option A270', 'Option B270', 'Option C270', 'Option D270'], 'answer': 'Option A270'}, {'question': 'Sample question 271?', 'options': ['Option A271', 'Option B271', 'Option C271', 'Option D271'], 'answer': 'Option A271'}, {'question': 'Sample question 272?', 'options': ['Option A272', 'Option B272', 'Option C272', 'Option D272'], 'answer': 'Option A272'}, {'question': 'Sample question 273?', 'options': ['Option A273', 'Option B273', 'Option C273', 'Option D273'], 'answer': 'Option A273'}, {'question': 'Sample question 274?', 'options': ['Option A274', 'Option B274', 'Option C274', 'Option D274'], 'answer': 'Option A274'}, {'question': 'Sample question 275?', 'options': ['Option A275', 'Option B275', 'Option C275', 'Option D275'], 'answer': 'Option A275'}, {'question': 'Sample question 276?', 'options': ['Option A276', 'Option B276', 'Option C276', 'Option D276'], 'answer': 'Option A276'}, {'question': 'Sample question 277?', 'options': ['Option A277', 'Option B277', 'Option C277', 'Option D277'], 'answer': 'Option A277'}, {'question': 'Sample question 278?', 'options': ['Option A278', 'Option B278', 'Option C278', 'Option D278'], 'answer': 'Option A278'}, {'question': 'Sample question 279?', 'options': ['Option A279', 'Option B279', 'Option C279', 'Option D279'], 'answer': 'Option A279'}, {'question': 'Sample question 280?', 'options': ['Option A280', 'Option B280', 'Option C280', 'Option D280'], 'answer': 'Option A280'}, {'question': 'Sample question 281?', 'options': ['Option A281', 'Option B281', 'Option C281', 'Option D281'], 'answer': 'Option A281'}, {'question': 'Sample question 282?', 'options': ['Option A282', 'Option B282', 'Option C282', 'Option D282'], 'answer': 'Option A282'}, {'question': 'Sample question 283?', 'options': ['Option A283', 'Option B283', 'Option C283', 'Option D283'], 'answer': 'Option A283'}, {'question': 'Sample question 284?', 'options': ['Option A284', 'Option B284', 'Option C284', 'Option D284'], 'answer': 'Option A284'}, {'question': 'Sample question 285?', 'options': ['Option A285', 'Option B285', 'Option C285', 'Option D285'], 'answer': 'Option A285'}, {'question': 'Sample question 286?', 'options': ['Option A286', 'Option B286', 'Option C286', 'Option D286'], 'answer': 'Option A286'}, {'question': 'Sample question 287?', 'options': ['Option A287', 'Option B287', 'Option C287', 'Option D287'], 'answer': 'Option A287'}, {'question': 'Sample question 288?', 'options': ['Option A288', 'Option B288', 'Option C288', 'Option D288'], 'answer': 'Option A288'}, {'question': 'Sample question 289?', 'options': ['Option A289', 'Option B289', 'Option C289', 'Option D289'], 'answer': 'Option A289'}, {'question': 'Sample question 290?', 'options': ['Option A290', 'Option B290', 'Option C290', 'Option D290'], 'answer': 'Option A290'}, {'question': 'Sample question 291?', 'options': ['Option A291', 'Option B291', 'Option C291', 'Option D291'], 'answer': 'Option A291'}, {'question': 'Sample question 292?', 'options': ['Option A292', 'Option B292', 'Option C292', 'Option D292'], 'answer': 'Option A292'}, {'question': 'Sample question 293?', 'options': ['Option A293', 'Option B293', 'Option C293', 'Option D293'], 'answer': 'Option A293'}, {'question': 'Sample question 294?', 'options': ['Option A294', 'Option B294', 'Option C294', 'Option D294'], 'answer': 'Option A294'}, {'question': 'Sample question 295?', 'options': ['Option A295', 'Option B295', 'Option C295', 'Option D295'], 'answer': 'Option A295'}, {'question': 'Sample question 296?', 'options': ['Option A296', 'Option B296', 'Option C296', 'Option D296'], 'answer': 'Option A296'}, {'question': 'Sample question 297?', 'options': ['Option A297', 'Option B297', 'Option C297', 'Option D297'], 'answer': 'Option A297'}, {'question': 'Sample question 298?', 'options': ['Option A298', 'Option B298', 'Option C298', 'Option D298'], 'answer': 'Option A298'}, {'question': 'Sample question 299?', 'options': ['Option A299', 'Option B299', 'Option C299', 'Option D299'], 'answer': 'Option A299'}, {'question': 'Sample question 300?', 'options': ['Option A300', 'Option B300', 'Option C300', 'Option D300'], 'answer': 'Option A300'}];